screenpresso.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy

**Learnpulse SAS values** your privacy and desires to ensure your experience with our websites and all our products, mobile applications, software, blogs, forums, channels and sharing services are as satisfying and safe as possible.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Learnpulse collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the www.screenpresso.com website and Screenpresso software (desktop).

Learnpulse SAS complies with the [General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection_en), the European Data Protection Law Enforcement Directive.

## Information you provide to Screenpresso website

Learnpulse collects the information you provide when you register to the Screenpresso newsletters, respond to surveys or when you buy licenses online. By providing us with this information, you consent to your information being collected and used by Learnpulse. Such information may include your:

name

address

e-mail

address

phone number

gender

IP address

The online store is operated by [2Checkout/Avangate](https://www.avangate.com/) company that is [GDPR compliant](https://www.avangate.com/lp/gdpr-compliant.html) (privacy policy).

## Navigational information

As you navigate the Website, Learnpulse may collect information through the use of cookies, including standard information from your web browser, your IP address, and the actions you take on Learnpulse’s Website or web beacons.

We use [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/) cookies to help us understand how visitors arrive at and browse our products and website to identify areas for improvement such as navigation, user experience, and marketing campaigns.

We ask user consent during the first website visit: the user can choose to disable Google analytics cookies as well as Youtube cookies.

The user may also block all cookies that have been saved on his computer by following the instructions of his browser on how to turn off cookies. If he blocks cookies it may be impossible to use some services or services can be degraded.

## Tracking Emails

We track clicks and open rates to measure the performance of our email campaigns. This information is used internally only to help us deliver relevant messaging, and is not shared with any third parties.

Emails are operated using [OVH France](https://www.ovh.com/) and Amazon Web Service AWS ([GDPR](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/gdpr-center/)).

Learnpulse collects information about how our customers use Screenpresso desktop application and the problems they may encounter. Learnpulse uses this information to improve the products, identify features that customers use most often and help them to solve problems.

Participation in the program is voluntary, and the end results are software improvements to better meet the needs of our customers. The user can choose to start or stop participating at any time in Screenpresso application settings. Those reports do not contain contact information, such as your name, address, or phone number.

We use an internal solution hosted on [OVH France](https://www.ovh.com/) as well as [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/) services for that purpose.

Our internal solution collects Screenpresso application analytics:

Screenpresso version

Number of the application runs with first and last usage dates

IP address

Country

Language

Windows version

.NET framework version

Our Google analytics solution collects Screenpresso application analytics:

Screenpresso version

Application start and stop dates

IP address

Country

Language

Windows version

.NET framework version

Computer hardware (screen size, available memory, etc…)

Analytics on feature usage -Analytics on installation and application instabilities

**We never collect or store any contents authored by using Screenpresso software: we never collect or store any screenshots nor videos from the end customers except when the user explicitly shares them through Screenpresso sharing options.**

Sharing Features Learnpulse collects information about shared contents when the customer uses Screenpresso cloud sharing feature:

the shared media (images or videos)

the IP address of the PC that upload the media

We do not collect any data when the customer uses third-party sharing features (Dropbox, Google drive, Evernote, …). Refer to corresponding private policy for third-parties.

Media (images or videos) are hosted on [Amazon S3](https://www.google.com/analytics/) in Ireland region.

## Performing the services requested

Learnpulse uses customer data to perform the services requested including:

To communicate practical information (Newsletters for example)

To improve customer service

To personalize user experience

To improve our website

To process payments

To run a promotion, contest, survey or other website feature

To provide content sharing features (Screenpresso cloud)

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers.

We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalfs, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

We use third-party services for operating Screenpresso services:

Website, file hosting, emailing services:

Amazon Web Service AWS ([GDPR](https://www.ovh.com/fr/protection-donnees-personnelles/gdpr.xml))

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over an SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Learnpulse has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

If you have questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at:

This document was last updated on August 21, 2018
